[
        {"question": "What is the derivative of x^n?", "answer": "n*x^(n-1)"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of r?", "answer": "0"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of e^x?", "answer": "e^x"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of b^x?", "answer": "ln(b)*b^x"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of sin(x)?", "answer": "cos(x)"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of cos(x)?", "answer": "-sin(x)"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of tan(x)?", "answer": "sec(x)^2"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of sec(x)?", "answer": "sec(x)*tan(x)"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of cot(x)?", "answer": "-csc(x)^2"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of csc(x)?", "answer": "-csc(x)*cot(x)"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of ln(x)?", "answer": "1/x"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of log_b(x)?", "answer": "1/(x*ln(b))"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of arcsin(x)?", "answer": "1/sqrt(1-x^2)"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of arccos(x)?", "answer": "-1/sqrt(1-x^2)"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of arctan(x)?", "answer": "1/(1+x^2)"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of arcsec(x)?", "answer": "1/(|x|*sqrt(x^2-1))"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of arccot(x)?", "answer": "-1/(1+x^2)"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of arccsc(x)?", "answer": "-1/(|x|*sqrt(x^2-1))"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of r*f(x)?", "answer": "r*f'(x)"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of f(x)+-g(x)?", "answer": "f'(x)+-g'(x)"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of f(x)*g(x)?", "answer": "f'(x)*g(x)+f(x)*g'(x)"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of f(x)/g(x)?", "answer": "(f'(x)*g(x)-f(x)*g'(x))/(g(x))^2"},
        {"question": "What is the derivative of f(g(x))?", "answer": "f'(g(x))*g'(x)"}
]